

GILLY HUGA ANARGYA

SOFTWARE ENGINNER

PROFILE

I'm a software engineer, with a strong interest in technology and good aesthetics. As a software engineer, My goal is to always build applications that are scalable and efficient under the hood while providing engaging, pixel-perfect user experiences.

CONTACT ME AT

+62 822-5774-9889

gilly.huga@yahoo.co.id

www.gillyhuga.xyz

in linkedin.com/in/gillyhuga/

SKILLS

PHP Research
HTML Analytics

CSS Android Studio

Java Web Development

MySQL Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back End Developer Intern PT. Inspirasi Mandiri Nusantara

— Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

 Create a Back-End website with Laravel Framework

Create a database using mySql

Work as a team using Git

Software Engineer Intern

Line Interior

— Jan 2018 – Apr 2018

Perfecting the Wordpress website

Create an android based catalog application with Ionic Framework

EDUCATION

INFORMATICS

University of Mumhammadiyah Malang | 2019 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Vocational High School 8 Malang | 2016 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

2nd Winner of Programming
PIM VII Competition 2019,
PIM STIKI MALANG

TRAINING HISTORY

VSGA JUNIOR MOBILE PROGRAMMING

Digital Talent Scholarship (Kominfo) |2019

ANDORID

SMK Coding (Aptika Kominfo) |2018

CERTIFICATION

BNSP JUNIOR MOBILE PROGRAMMER

Badan Nasional Sertifikasi (BNSP) |2019-2021